I think it's got to happen again, guys.
I'm not really stoked about it, but I
think we have to move Laser Boy Hollow
again. Landlord has raised the rent. My
lease is up in 2 months, and I've
already been struggling here for the
past 3 months. Honestly, it's been
tricky. The social media game, the art
game, it's been really tricky. And now
the economyy's going all the way down.
So, what are we doing? We got to problem
solve. I don't want to close shop.
That's the nightmare for me. We've been
here before. I think the downwards flip
has been mostly about me not paying
attention to all of the media things
you're supposed to be paying attention
to and how you're supposed to adjust and
how you're supposed to do things. As
well as me severely being adverse to
things like the Tik Tok shop and other
commerce platforms that try and
get creators or influencers to sell
stupid But luckily I do have a
place to land. So, this is the third
iteration of the laser boy hollow laser
lab situation. I've been comfortable
here for 2 years and now we're on to the
next the next one. Rebuild again. We got
a lot of the stuff here. It should be
quicker and easier. It doesn't travel
2,000 mi across the country. We just got
to travel about 3 mi in one direction
and then we'll be all right. So, where
are we
going to here? New basement. This is the
basement of my lovely girlfriends and
these are her kils. She's a ceramic
artist. She's going to be setting up in
this side. I'm going be on this side.
We're going to be kind of dueling it,
right? That sounds kind of cool. I got
to move stuff and do a lot of stuff. And
I'm dancing around this pole. Not for
money, but I do need money. Okay, it's
been about a week since I shot that
first part of this video. And now I just
have to get going cuz I feel like
there's specific things here that are
stopping me from getting momentum and
getting this place situated so that I
can start working in it. Start making
stuff for you and all that good stuff.
Uh, I got to paint it. I don't want to
paint it. Got to paint it though. I
think that I'm motivated enough to do
it. Hope that I can keep momentum and
let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
In the plan of no return with move here.
We're going to move that table and this
whole thing. That means that the next
batch of film that I make has to be the
new spot. And I got a couple orders that
I got to do. So, it means that I got to
make the rest of this whole thing pretty
swift.
So, here we are. I think we're in lab
four. Boom. Here we are. Uh, maybe we
should give you a wider view here. Looks
kind of like this.
Uh, yeah. I guess we could maybe zoom in
a little bit.
Um, I don't know what I feel about this
light yet. Maybe it's okay. This is a
new lab, so I clean this stuff up, but
like I said, let's get to work. It's not
going to be perfect. Uh, just better
every day, right? So, come here. Here we
are. Nice. So, this is just how the
set's going to work. We're going to do
the live content. We're going to do
recorded content. We're going to do
content, right? Content's the name of
the game and the art game today. But the
idea here is that to be present. The
world is very weird right now. And I
think that artificial let's say
artificial creators do pose a threat to
the creator economy in general. I think
there is a way that we marry together
this beautiful future. Uh but right now
it seems like artists are being taken
advantage of. AI is only built for tech
boys who don't want to pay creative. So
I'm a mixture of a tech boy and a
creative. So I use the technology. I'm
up with the technology. I don't really
know how we navigate forward, but I do
know that I need to be present as a
human creator. And I think this is how
we do it. I think like we'll do this
type of uh content, this type of like
just open creativity, I think is the
concept that I have in mind. I've got a
lot of projects knocking around,
floating around. Point being is that
like I don't think that in this world of
AI generation and duping other people's
work, there's any value in just posting
a final image, right? A final piece of
art, right? and showing the process is
really what it's all about. Like
especially when you do with the work
that I do, which is that it's holography
and it's not necessarily widely known
how it works or how it's made. I think
this just a way to get ahead of the
curve, get as close to being
undeniably here and human and creative
as I can, which seems to be live
streaming. This is what I learned to do
on Tik Tok. Uh, Tik Tok was really cool
because I got to like directly connect
with people. Uh, doing the live streams.
It was very nice having like a a
community to tune into, people that
cared, people that were interested, and
I just want to keep growing that even if
it's not on Tik Tok. That's why we're
here on YouTube. Um, we're also going to
be streaming on other platforms like Tik
Tok, too, but I don't think as much like
I don't think it's going to be the
primary place. trying to figure out
right now I do have it set up so that I
can stream horizontally like this to
YouTube as well as Tik Tok vertically at
the same time. So that's really cool. I
have a system in place where I can be in
more places at once. Uh and we can
expand that even more. I think that's
dependent on my upload speed, my my
internet here. So look forward to more
online content, live content that but
it's cool to have a platform where
people can just step in and start asking
me questions and I can speak directly to
them. I think that talking to people is
way to way to talk to them about art. So
that's why I always try when I can to
have a call with my clients so we on the
same page and uh and uh sometimes we get
there, sometimes we don't. Anyway, I'm
just rambling now. Please tune in. We're
going to do these I don't know what
schedule's going to be. Maybe Tuesdays
and Thursdays we're going to be doing
some
streaming. Maybe suggestions on when
people are available. If you're watching
this video, you seem like an interesting
party. Interested party. It's
intersection. Uh I'll catch you later.
I'm gonna go I'm going to be working on
a pendant, a hologram pendant of a Luna
moth. The model is almost
done. So, this is what we're doing here.
This is what we're doing. It's going to
be one of the kind of guillotine style
pendants that I make. I don't know why
that's the move. Um, but uh it is now a
sultan like what I do here. If you I'm
trying to get back on all the
instas, right? Uh I think that it was
really difficult to operate
as me. I'll just say me, right? It was
difficult to operate as me the tail end
of last year, right? I don't think that
I did well with the news cycle. I don't
think that I think that overall I am too
sensitive for the news. I don't know
what to do about that other than to
continue to translate my emotions into
my work. So internal renaissance, right?
I think that I'm just giving myself the
authority to step back into the light.
uh try to accept the idea that the
things that I create are worth people's
time and they're important. If you
follow me on Instagram for a long time,
if you found me on Tik Tok, if you found
me on YouTube, I don't care where you
found me. I just really appreciate that
that you're here. And hopefully we're
going to turn this car around. We're
going to go uphill now. Thank you.